geoeye.com 2012-12-30

# GeoEye › Privacy Policy

GeoEye believes that a strong electronic-privacy policy is crucial to the ongoing growth and success of the Internet as a service, a commercial tool, and an entertainment medium. GeoEye ("GeoEye," "we," "our," and the like) is committed to protecting your privacy online. To better protect your privacy, we provide you with this notice (the "Privacy Policy") explaining our online information practices for the GeoEye.com Web site (the "Site") and the choices that you can make about the way your information is collected and used on our Site. 

GeoEye utilizes the following practices to safeguard any information that is provided to us by users of this Web site. You may also change the status of your stated desire to receive GeoEye special offers or communications at any time. 

##  1\. The Information We Collect

On our Site, you can submit comments and questions about our products and services, and you can request to be added to our Alerts e-mail list. 

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '98, Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., AOL, Earthlink). 

In order to fulfill licensing transactions or to provide service to you as a customer of GeoEye, we may require that you provide certain information to us. Common items may include, but are not limited to, your name, address, phone number, and credit card number.

##  2\. How We Use the Information

By providing this information to GeoEye, you are agreeing to allow us to utilize this information to complete all transactions that you request through this Web site and to disclose that information and the details of all such transactions to GeoEye's various worldwide offices, subsidiaries, affiliates, and any necessary payment processors. Because of the nature of the Internet, such data may pass through any country. 

We may also use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you about updates to our products and services, or to assist you with questions you may have about an order you have placed for products and services. From time to time, we may use the personally identifiable information that we collect to offer you other products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

In order to improve the content of our Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience, we collect information regarding which pages consumers access or which files that they download. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Site usage, as well as to offer you products or services. We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process as permitted by relevant laws, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena in response to a law-enforcement agency's request. GeoEye's agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for GeoEye.

##  3\. Choices We Provide You

We may contact you to provide you with opportunities to purchase products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive marketing information from this Site, please send an e-mail to that effect to [info@geoeye.com](mailto:info@geoeye.com?subject=Privacy) .

##  4\. Collection of Information By Others

Our Site contains links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

##  5\. About Cookies

When you visit parts of the GeoEye Web site, you may receive a text file called a "cookie" located in the browser directory of your computer's hard drive. A cookie is a small piece of information that a Web site can store on your computer for use by your Web browser. The cookie cannot be read by any Web site other than the one that created the cookie. Cookies enable this Site to recognize and remember information that you consented to give this Site, such as customer information for purchases or visits to portions of this Site that are most appropriate for your professional needs. As a result, the cookies should allow you to retrieve previous information and invoices. Your credit card information will NOT be stored in the cookie or in our various databases. Other functionality may be included in the future to make your online experience more efficient and personable.

We do NOT use cookies to track or examine your surfing behavior before or after leaving the GeoEye Web site. For more information on cookies, you can point your browser to [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).

##  6\. How You Can Review Your Information

If you would like to review the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you online, just let us know by sending us an e-mail at [webmaster@geoeye.com](mailto:webmaster@geoeye.com?subject=Privacy) , and we will provide you with a copy of the information that you provided.

##  7\. How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy for this Site, you may contact us at 2325 Dulles Corner Boulevard, Herndon, VA 20171, or via e-mail at [webmaster@geoeye.com](mailto:webmaster@geoeye.com?subject=Privacy) .

##  8\. Terms of Use

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference in our Terms of Use, which set forth your rights and responsibilities and the terms and conditions that govern your use of this Site and its associated services. To review the Terms of Use, please click here, or click on the "Terms and Conditions" link at the bottom of each page on the Site.
